ucaster.eu 2017-12-11

# Privacy policy

**General**

Ucaster is committed to protecting your privacy when you use the Ucaster website. This Privacy Policy informs you of the types of information Ucaster collects about you, how that information is used, whether and to whom Ucaster discloses it, and the choices you have regarding your personal information. Please read carefully. 

**Collection of Information**

Ucaster may automatically collect certain aggregated data regarding your use of the website. Aggregated information is anonymous, statistical information that reflects the scope of the website's user base, sales, customer patterns and related site information. In addition, certain non-personally identifiable information is collected by Ucaster and other third-party advertising providers during your use of the Ucaster website and in serving advertisements to the Ucaster website.

Ucaster may also use cookies to track and understand the traffic on the Ucaster website. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that the Ucaster website places onto the user's computer hard drive. Cookies identify the user's computer hard drive so that the Ucaster website can recognize you the next time you visit.

Third party advertisements displayed on or in connection with the Ucaster website may also contain cookies set by such advertisers. Ucaster does not control these cookies and users of the Ucaster website should check the privacy policy of such advertisers to understand whether  
and how it uses cookies. 

**Use of Information**

If you submit personally identifiable information to Ucaster through the Ucaster website, then Ucaster may use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the site.

Ucaster does not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. Ucaster may, however, use  
your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes 

**Disclosure of Information**

Ucaster may share aggregated statistical information and profile information about users of the Ucaster website with third-parties, including distributors, vendors, advertisers actual and potential customers and business partners. This information is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

Ucaster will not share your personally identifiable information with any third-parties for their commercial or marketing use without your consent  
or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out.

Ucaster may release personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with any laws or respond to a court order, subpoena, or search warrant.

Ucaster also reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information that, in good faith, if appropriate or necessary to enforce the Terms of Use, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend itself against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of the Ucaster website, and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Ucaster, our users or others. 

**Changes and updates to this Privacy Notice**

This privacy notice may be revised periodically and users are encouraged to review it periodically to stay aware of any changes. Your continued use of the Ucaster website constitutes your agreement to this privacy notice and any future revisions.
